Yes, so the top of ICICI Lombard can
fall tomorrow and why it can fall, we will
talk about it in this video
and will go into
how much investment should be made in ICICI Lombard or not,
let's start,
yes, the news here is that
a company which is doing extra tax is going to
sell its candidate example at 3.57 in the list tomorrow and if we talk about the hot price order, then they are going to
sell it between 2097 to 1576 and see, today's
closing price is 1576 only, so
if you look at the market, but if you
take out about three and a half paise, that is, if the
plotting of three and a half percent is high in the market, then
automatically we will see the price of a used top
falling, so the
question arises here that
if you see every one or two days, then sometimes
someone is bringing money in HDFC Life, sometimes it is coming
in HDFC AMC, sometimes it is coming
in Life, sometimes it is coming in SBI Card, so this has happened
and that  Look,
if we mainly look at this sector, this
company is General Insurance Chandra, then the
competition mode is increasing here, the
applications will increase here, so
Juhi, an exponential growth, that is, the
double-digit growth that this company
packs, we do not
get to see it here, but let's see that
where this double-digit growth
is available, we invested there, but the
general insurance sector is currently
penetrated and the
penetration is increasing there, there is no doubt
that this sector will grow, but if there is an
explanation, the
sector can show a growth of 20-30 percent daily, this is a
big question that arises here,
because of this, if you see, there are
seals etc. being organized here and this
company is spreading on premium valuation, then
we can also see one region here,
now look at this, the
market cap of this company is Rs 7721 crore,
if we talk about the price, then it is
behind sixty-three times.  The top three
doors are if you look at the validation for
interview, if you look at it here, it is a
little page that they are but it was seen getting a stop here,
if we
talk about price tourists then it is also coming up
nine times, something like this, this conservation,
we used to see it as an undervalued one,
if we look at it, for the last 4 years there has been no
use in a small fraction and the profitability of the company is seen
increasing very well for the last four years
and the way the penetration
is increasing here and especially in health
insurance because
due to Kuwait, the demand for health insurance has
increased, due to this
they are getting very good premium collection here
and because of this good
profitability point, now it was also
seen good for the company here, now
look at 1576 dear stock today close My and today
see, it has seen a slight increase
but Nifty is around 150 points
up and it did not close above the top 1 percent,
worry you will see its all  All time
high of 1675, if we compare it to
RO Nagar in percentage wise, if we talk then
67 percent was getting correction from its all time interest, that if it will be
BTech, then
about 3 to 4 percent, send a talk can fall further,
see if you are a conservative investor
then definitely you can invest
10 to 15 percent capital application,
if you want it on Rauniyar Vaishya, then you
can invest here in my channel now,
but if you invest aggressively and want
a high returns top, then there is a
medical check or some other option here, I could have said that
if we look at it aggressively, there is a lot of competition in general insurance, in
reality there are not that many players,
but if we look at it in reality, there are 34
more players here and in the coming
time, that player can also be
one person, this is what I see here,
you must have liked this small news video, if you have any
variation, then please comment, I will definitely
reply to your comment, okay friends,
thank you, I have a  Nice DP